http://www.rbza.com/privacy.aspx

Privacy Notice - RBZ&A Custom Software and Web Application Development
Contact Us
Application Design and DevelopmentCustom development with Microsoft Technologies
Custom Web ApplicationsDesign, Development, Integration, Conversion, Maintenance
eCommerce Application DevelopmentGrow your online business
Database Development and DesignThe base to build upon
Conversions & Systems IntegrationMigrate from old technology
Mobile App developmentLet us build your next mobile adventure
Consulting ServicesLet us help you with your software and web application needs
Case Study - Intelligent digital business card.
Client GalleryPartial List of Our Clients
Case StudiesView Our Current and Past Projects
TestimonialsOur Clients speak for themselves
Case Study - LA Opera Rebuilds Ticketing System.
About UsCustom development with Microsoft Technologies
Fact SheetDesign, Development, Integration, Conversion, Maintenance
HistoryBulding Business Application that work Since 1981
Technical ExpertiseStrong Skills & A Solid Track Record
PartnersStrategic Partnerships Make a Difference
CareersJump Start Your Career
Case Study - MegaPath Customer Portal Reporting.
Home
/
Privacy Statement
Request a Quick Quote
Want to Provide More Information?
Privacy Notice
When you visit the R.B. Zack & Associates, Inc. website, we may collect and store the following information about you: the name of the domain from which you access the Internet; the date and time you access the site; and the Internet address of the web site from which you linked directly to the site, and the pages you visit.  We use this information for internal purposes, which may include measuring the number of visitors to different sections of the site, and who referred the visitor to us, which helps us keep the site relevant and useful.
If you identify yourself to us by sending an e-mail or submitting a form, we collect and store your e-mail address and any other information you provide.  If you give us permission to send information to you, we will tailor the correspondence we send according to your preferences.  If you do not want us to contact you, please let us know via the means below. This is also the best way to inform us if your information or preferences have changed.
All of the information we collect about you is for internal purposes only.  We will not sell or give away this information.  However, per your request, we may send information on third-party events or other items that may be of interest to you.
Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of any data or information you send to us.
We may contact you periodically to confirm that you still want to receive information from us.  We don't believe in spamming people that don't want to hear from us.
We currently use cookies, but only for tracking site performance.  In the future, we may use them in ways that will make site navigation easier for returning visitors.  For example, we might use cookies so you don't have to login multiple times.  But we don't believe in the use of spyware.
This privacy policy was last updated on December 10, 2010. When changes to our privacy policy take place, we plan to notify active members of our database via email.
You can contact us with questions and comments at:
R. B. Zack & Associates, Inc.
Copyright 2020 © R.B. Zack & Associates, Inc. All rights reserved. Privacy Notice
